Varicose veins and Mediclaim: Today we are not going to discuss the topic
of whether your treatment will be taxed or
not. In this video, we will
give you more information about it.
Varicose vein surgery is not a cosmetic surgery,
so it is taxed under Mediclaim.
It is not like other laser treatments done by
dermatologists or dermatologists.
Those laser treatments are
not taxed under Mediclaim. But
laser treatment of Varicose veins is
taxed under Mediclaim. Today,
almost 80 to 90% of our treatment
is through Mediclaim cover facility, but
this is not taxed in the policy. So,
this will be taxed only after your minimum 2 years policy is completed. Because Varicose veins
treatment
[sangeet]
[sangeet] is done
by the hospital and you get
initial approval, which means that the patient can be
admitted and their surgery can be done.
Then your final bill is sent and a
final approval comes. Sometimes there are some deductions
or some small deductions in the final amount
which  Perhaps you may have to pay.
We try to make it completely cashless at the Vascular Centre,
meaning the patient does
not have to pay a single penny from the time he enters the hospital till he leaves. The second option is
reimbursement,
meaning in this you first deposit the money
in the hospital and then you submit those papers
to your mediclaim company from where the
money is credited to your account. The
patient faces a lot of trouble in this, has to
make multiple rounds, multiple
letters are required and the payment comes after one to two months
and that too not the full amount. So
friends, if you want to get
treatment done,
you can come to us for cashless facility. We have a
complete medical team who will give you complete
cashless approval and
your treatment can be done without a single penny. Thank you
[Sangeet]